-天啊，为什么还没完?-等一下，好吗?
- God, why won't it stop? - Just give it a second, will you?
你在哪里?你应该在六点以前到家。
Where were you? You should have been home by six.
我告诉过你们今晚我要和艾米一起做作业。
I told you guys I was doing homework with Amy tonight.
那里发生了什么事?你受伤了吗?
What happened there? Did you hurt yourself?
艾米的猫抓伤了我。它很好。
Amy's, uh, cat scratched me. It's fine.
-没什么大不了的。-你为什么不接我电话?
- It's no big deal. - Why weren't you answering my calls?
我很抱歉，我只是…
Look I'm sorry, I just...
我想是ef5。
I think it's an ef5.
这不是龙卷风，宝贝。
It's not a tornado, baby.
-可能是ef5。- ef5到底是什么?
- It might be an ef5. - What the hell is an ef5?
就像当两个龙卷风相遇时，
It's like when two tornadoes come together,
形成了一个巨大的龙卷风。
and they form one giant tornado.
-它把路上的一切东西都撕碎了。-天啊，真的吗?
- It rips everything in its path. - God, is that true?
不，只是雷雨而已。一切都会没事的。
No, it's just a thunderstorm. Everything's gonna be okay.
天啊，太吵了。
Jesus, that was loud.
有点吵。
It was a little loud.
听起来像枪声。
Sounded like a gunshot.
也许是ef6。等待。
Maybe it's an ef6. Wait.
真的有ef6这样的东西吗?
Is there even such a thing as ef6?
宝贝，不会有龙卷风的。
Baby, there's not gonna be a tornado.
只是一场雷雨，很快就会过去的。
It's just a thunderstorm, and it's going to pass.
大多数事情都会结束的，不是吗?
Most things come to an end, don't they?
妈妈，我觉得有点不对劲。
Mom, I think something might be wrong.
就像风暴一样，一些糟糕的事情可能正在发生。
Like with the storm, something bad might be happening.
不,它会通过。
No, it'll pass.
谁想玩酒店大逃亡?
Who wants to play the great hotel escape?
-我们玩的时候你永远都看不懂牌。-我识字!
- You can never read the cards when we play that. - I can read!
-男人…-妈，告诉她我识字。
- Guys... - Mom, tell her I can read.
梅尔，你哥哥识字。
Mel, your brother can read.
看!我告诉你。
See! I told you.
-妈，你看到梅尔…!——够了!
- Mom, did you see what Mel...! - Enough!
- - - - - -那是谁?——没有人。
- Who's that? - Nobody.
正确的。
Right.
谁想扮演哥特人和破坏者?
Who wants to play goths and vandals?
-不是很棒的酒店逃亡吗?-现在不行，宝贝。
- Not the great hotel escape? - Not right now, baby.
听着，我们就玩哥特和破坏者的游戏。
Look we just pull out the goths and vandals game.
我打赌等我们过了第一轮，
I bet you by the time we get through the first round,
暴风雨会过去的。
the storm will've passed.
除非龙卷风把我们的房子卷走
Unless the tornado picks up our house
-然后把它带走之类的。- - - - - -闭嘴!
- and carries it away or something. - Shut up!
那只发生在《绿野仙踪》里。
That only happened in the wizard of oz.
这也可能发生在这里。
It could happen here too.
天啊，你真蠢。
God, you're so dumb.
我不是跟你说过不要那样跟你哥哥说话吗?
What did I tell you about talking to your brother like that?
对不起。
Sorry.
是吗?
Are you?
——是哪一位?-只是没人。
- Who's calling? - It's just nobody.
-是啊，谁打来的?——没有人!
- Yeah, who's calling? - Nobody!
哈!
Huh!
你真觉得这个厕所能保护我们吗
You really think this bathroom is gonna protect us
从一个巨大的，古老的龙卷风俯冲下来…
from a big, old tornado that swoops in and...
你真觉得这会有什么区别吗?
You really think it's gonna make any difference at all?
如果你不想和我们在一起，
Well if you don't wanna be in here with us,
-你知道门在哪。——哦!现在我有一个选择。
- you know where the door is. - Oh! Now I have a choice.
这是怎么回事?
What is going on?
嘘。没关系。没关系。
Shh. It's okay. It's okay.
灯为什么灭了?
Why did the lights go out?
伙计们，这是雷雨，
You guys, it's a thunderstorm,
闪电可能击中了变压器之类的东西。
lightning probably hit a transformer or something.
不要无缘无故地惊慌失措。
Stop freaking out for no reason.
这是一个龙卷风!这是一个龙卷风!这是一个龙卷风!
It's a tornado! It's a tornado! It's a tornado!
鲍比?
Bobby?
闪电击中房子了吗?!
Did lightning hit the house?!
-那是什么鬼东西?天啊，那是什么?——耶稣基督。
- What the hell was that? Oh, god, what was that? - Jesus Christ.
我不知道。我不知道。
I don't know. I don't know.
爸爸不!不要去。
Dad no! Don't go.
把灯打开，好吗?
Just get the light, okay?
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
——怎么了?-打不开。
- What's wrong? - It won't open.
打不开是什么意思?
What do you mean it won't open?
我是说打不开!
I mean it won't fucking open!
梅丽莎，把手机给我。
Melissa, give me your phone.
——没有。什么?为什么?-把电话给我
- No. What? Why? - Just give me the goddamn phone.
哦，搞什么?
Oh, what the fuck?
该死的!
God damn it!
-什么事?——树。
- What is it? - A tree.
——什么?-我想是棵该死的树
- A what? - I think a fucking tree
-挡住了门。-哦,上帝。
- is blocking the door. - Oh, god.
什么树?你不能移动它?
What tree? You can't move it?
我看起来能移动它吗?他妈的!
Does it look like I can move it? Fuck!
也许是后院的一棵树。
Maybe it's a tree from the backyard.
——什么?-我们埋的地方。
- What? - Where we buried spot.
- - - - - -什么? !——啊!
- What?! - Ugh!
妈的，梅尔。
God damn it, Mel.
-斑点死了吗?-我们一会儿再谈，好吗?
- Is spot dead? - Let's talk about this in a minute, okay?
但是小不点跑了!小不点跑了!
- But spot ran away! - Spot ran away!
该死的。
God damn it.
——耶稣基督。-我的手机呢?
- Jesus Christ. - Where's my phone?
——冷静下来。-爸爸，我的手机呢?
- Calm down. - Dad, where's my phone?
-我掉了。——啊!
- I dropped it. - Ugh!
你能不能别这么歇斯底里?这是一个风暴。
Would you stop being hysterical? It's a storm.
艾米很好。耶稣基督。
Amy is fine. Jesus Christ.
又不是世界末日。
It's not the end of the goddamn world.
梅尔!把门关上!
Mel! Shut the door!
把门关上!
Close the door!
-我们卡住了吗?-我不知道。屋顶不见了。
- Are we stuck? - I don't know. The roof is gone.
哦,我的上帝。到这里来。
Oh, my god. Come here.
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我们得做点什么，不是吗?
We have to do something, don't we?
不是吗?
Don't we?
伙计们!
Guys!
我想我们还是等吧。
I guess we wait.
艾米……
Amy...
我还在等你停下呢，
Hey, I was waiting for you to stop,
看台后面?
back by the bleachers?
哦，对不起，我没看见你。
Oh, sorry, I didn't see you.
但你看到了别的东西，不是吗?
But you saw something else, didn't you?
-我很抱歉我不是故意的。-不是故意的?
- I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to... - Didn't mean to what?
盯着看吗?
Stare?
也许我想让你这么做。
Maybe I wanted you to.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我以前是个切割工。
I used to be a cutter.
为什么?
Why?
因为我曾经死了。
Because I used to be dead.
情况有多糟?这棵树吗?
How bad is it? The tree?
你认为保险公司会赔偿吗?
You think the insurance will cover it?
我不知道。
I don't know.
你要再打一次电话吗?
You gonna try your phone again?
等等，爸爸，我能用一下你的电话吗?打电话给艾米。
Wait, dad, can I use your phone? To call Amy.
它有问题。试一试你的。
Something's wrong with it. Try yours.
哦,我不能。
Oh, I can't.
——你不能?-是的，我不能。它死了。
- You can't? - Yeah, I can't. It's dead.
哦，该死的。
Oh, god damn it.
他妈的一坨屎。
Fucking piece of shit.
——嗯…——什么?
- Uh... - What?
我想看看新闻，
Well, I'm trying to check the news,
但这该死的东西不管用。
but this fucking thing isn't working.
好吧,嗯…你想让我看看吗?
Okay, well... do you want me to have a look at it?
不，我不想让你看。
No, I don't want you to have a look at it.
好吧。我只是问问。
Okay. I was just asking.
爸爸，我能试试你的手机吗?
Dad, can I please try your phone?
我要尿尿。
I have to pee.
我不能跟你们一起去。
I can't go with you guys here.
我不知道该跟你说什么，梅尔。
I don't know what to tell you, Mel.
我还能听到你尿尿的声音，妹妹。
I can still hear you pee, sis.
天啊，鲍比，天啊!
Oh, my god, Bobby, Jesus!
哇，真的是ef5。
Wow, it was really an ef5.
是的。可能是吧。
Yeah. It might have been.
你们觉得现在就结束了?
You guys think it's over now?
你觉得有人死了吗?
Do you think people died?
不，宝贝，没人死。
No, baby, nobody died.
这是非常可能的。
It's very possible.
严重吗?
Seriously?
嘿,你们!我看见一条蛇!
Hey, you guys! I see a snake!
- - - - - -什么? !鲍比，快离开那里。——在哪里?
- What?! Bobby get away from there. - Where?
在那边，梳妆台都被打碎了。
Over there, where the dressers all smashed.
我什么也没看到。
I don't see anything.
我想这是一条响尾蛇。
I think it's a rattlesnake.
你对响尾蛇了解多少?
What do you know about rattlesnakes?
在这里。
It's right there.
鲍比，没有蛇。
Bobby, there's no snake.
鲍比，进去，把门关上。
Bobby, get inside and shut the door.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我曾经在YouTube上看到一条响尾蛇。
I saw a rattlesnake on YouTube once.
它正在吃鳄鱼。
It was eating an alligator.
什么?
What?
没有响尾蛇吃过短吻鳄。
No rattlesnake's ever eaten an alligator.
那是一只小鳄鱼。
It was a baby alligator.
那是只小鳄鱼，当然。
Oh, well it was a baby alligator, sure.
当然，这很有道理。
Of course, that makes perfect sense.
你以前应该告诉我的。
You should have mentioned that before.
我这辈子见过的蛇都是吃老鼠的
The only snakes that I ever met in my life eat mice
和其他狗屎。
and other shit.
-别那样看着我。-真不敢相信你把它掉了。
- Don't look at me like that. - Can't believe you dropped it.
这是一场意外。
It was an accident.
那我们现在要怎么离开这里?
Well, how are we supposed to get out of here now?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我们就不能把门砸开吗?那墙呢?
Can't we just break the door down? What about the wall?
——墙上?-墙，门还是别的什么。
- The wall? - The wall or the door or whatever.
你就不能在上面钻个洞爬出来吗?
Can't you just bust a hole through it and crawl out?
我们可以……
Can we just...
-我不…如何?与什么?-我不知道。
- I don't... how? With what? - I don't know.
你就不能打穿它吗?
Can't you just punch through it or something?
不，我不能打穿它。
No, I can't just punch through it.
那东西是橡木做的。
That thing is made of solid oak.
那是钢化玻璃砖。那是一堵石墙。
That is tempered glass blocks. That is a rock wall.
这是瓷砖。这些墙有六英尺厚。
This is tile. These walls are six feet thick.
我们他妈要怎么做?
How the fuck are we supposed to do that?
你想把手弄断吗?
You wanna break your hand?
——看,每个人都…-请便。
- Look, everyone... - Be my guest.
一切都会好的。没那么久。
Everything's going to be fine. It hasn't been that long.
有人会来。
Someone will come.
耶稣基督,盲目乐观。
Jesus Christ, pollyanna.
如果这不仅仅是一场风暴呢，妈妈?
What if it wasn't just a storm, mom?
外面有人吗?
Is there anybody out there?
-我们需要这个。——需要什么?
- We need that. - Need what?
我们需要它来保持水分。
We need it to stay hydrated.
但我还没看完呢。
But I'm not finished with it yet.
你能吗?
Well, can you be?
在这里,宝贝。
Here, baby.
-我洗掉了，别担心。——但是妈妈……
- I washed it out, don't worry. - But mom...
把水喝了吧，鲍比!只是喝!
Just drink the water, Bobby! Just drink it!
什么，我现在没有了吗?
What, I don't get any now?
别紧张，我只是随便玩玩。
Relax, I'm just fucking around.
有什么事吗?你开不起玩笑了吗?
What's the matter? You can't take a joke any more?
嘿，你为什么不冷静点?
Hey, why don't you just chill out?
嘿，我只是玩玩而已。
Hey, I'm just messing around.
别每次我说…
Don't overreact every time I say...
听着，该死的。
Listen, god damn it.
我们堆的东西已经够多了
We have enough shit piling up here
-没有你的体重。-你在说什么?
- without your weight added to it. - What are you talking about?
你很清楚我在说什么。
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
所以别突然装无辜了。
So don't try acting innocently all of a sudden.
-迪…-你想打架吗?很好。
- Dee... - Look, you wanna fight? Fine.
等这一切结束再说吧，因为现在，
Save it for when this is all over because right now,
没人想听。
nobody wants to hear it.
哇。
Whoa.
不。你有6 ?
No. You have a six?
是的。在这里。
Yeah. Here.
妈妈,我饿了。
Mom, I'm hungry.
是的,我也是。
Yeah, me too.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
真希望我们带了金鱼饼干什么的。
I wish we'd brought some goldfish crackers with us or something.
啊!金鱼饼干真恶心。
Ugh! Goldfish crackers are disgusting.
嗯。对我来说更多。
Hmm. More for me then.
我想要一些鸡蛋。我要一千个鸡蛋。奶酪。
I want some eggs. I want a thousand eggs. With cheese.
-真恶心，只有老人才喜欢吃鸡蛋，鲍比。-不，他们没有。
- Gross, only old people like eggs, Bobby. - No, they don't.
妈妈，告诉姐姐所有人都喜欢鸡蛋。
Mom, tell sis all types of people like eggs.
梅丽莎，所有人都喜欢吃鸡蛋。
Melissa, all types of people like eggs.
Nuh-uh。只有老人。
Nuh-uh. Only old people.
你知道那意味着什么吗，鲍比?
And you know what that makes you, Bobby?
-别说了…-你知道那意味着什么吗?
- Don't say it... - You know what that makes you?
妈妈，告诉妹妹别这么说。
Mom, tell sis not to say it.
-梅丽莎，别说了——好吧,好吧。
- Melissa, don't say it. - Okay, okay.
这让你看起来像个小老头。
It makes you a tiny, old man.
妈妈！
Mom!
冷静下来。没关系。
Calm down. It's okay.
-一个瘦小的老人。——愚蠢的混蛋。
- A tiny, old man. - Stupid asshole.
他妈的!他妈的!
Fuck! Fuck!
他妈的一坨屎!
Fucking piece of shit!
这该死的电池!
Stupid fucking battery!
你他妈的没用的混蛋科技!
You fucking useless asshole technology!
你他妈的婊子!去你妈的!
You fucking cunt! Fuck you!
你混蛋!去死吧，你这该死的婊子!
You motherfucker! Die, you fucking bitch!
你这笨蛋!去你妈的!
You stupid cunt! Fuck you!
操你的屁股!
Fuck you in your ass!
为什么还没有人来?
Why hasn't anybody come yet?
我不知道。
I don't know.
不是一个龙卷风。
Not a tornado.
别的东西。
Something else.
你的意思是……?
You mean...?
我认为……
I think...
这没有任何意义。
It doesn't make any sense.
什么不合理?
What doesn't make any sense?
我们的邻居。有人已经来了。
We have neighbors. Someone would've come.
看到这棵树。
Seen the tree.
为什么没有呢，爸爸?
Why haven't they, daddy?
他们都死了。
They're all dead.
你为什么这么说?
Why would you say that?
或者他们已经被疏散了。
Or they've already been evacuated.
不管怎样，这对我们来说都不是好兆头。
Either way, it doesn't bode too well for any of us.
我曾经死了。
I used to be dead.
大多数人。他们只是没有意识到。
Most people are. They just don't realize it.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
他们说我疯了。我这么做是为了引起注意。
They said I was crazy. That I did it for attention.
你听说过胆小鬼妄想吗?
You ever heard of cotard delusion?
不，我不这么认为。
No, I don't think so.
骨瘦如柴的综合症。
Walking corpse syndrome.
我想这就像一种精神疾病。
It's like a mental illness, I guess.
人们开始相信他们真的死了。
People become convinced that they're actually really dead.
这就是你以前割自己的原因吗?
Is that why you used to cut yourself?
如果我还能流血，也许我就能提醒自己那不是真的，
If I could still bleed, then maybe I could remind myself that it wasn't real,
我还活着
that I was still alive.
你想成为吗?
Did you want to be?
当你割伤自己的时候，你希望看到什么?
When you would cut yourself, what were you hoping to see?
梅那看起来像是被感染了
Mel, that's starting to look infected.
它很好。
It's fine.
我在上面放点东西，好吗?
I'm gonna put something on it, okay?
妈妈，爸爸，我饿了。
Mom, dad, I'm hungry.
好吧，我不知道该说什么。
Okay, I don't know what to say about that.
我要一个火腿芝士煎蛋卷。
I want an omelet with ham and cheese.
但是娘娘腔没有奶酪，听到了吗，姐姐?
But sissy doesn't get any cheese, you hear that, sis?
哦,我的上帝。哦,我的上帝。什么，什么，什么，什么?
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. What, what, what, what?
我的天，我的天，我的天，我的天，我的天!
Oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god!
鲍比，你待在那里。
Bobby, you stay there.
-这他妈…——哦,耶稣。什么?
- What the f... - Oh, Jesus. What?
-鲍比，到浴缸里去!-我的天啊!
- Bobby, get in the tub! - Oh, my god!
——好吧,好吧。呆在那里。呆在那里。-我的天啊。
- Okay, okay. Stay there. Stay there. - Oh, my god.
狗屎!
Shit!
哦,我的上帝。我的天，我的天，我的天!
Oh, my god. Oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god!
好吧。好吧，我去找你。等一等。
Okay. Okay, I'm coming to you. Hold on.
-我的天啊。-罗伯特…
- Oh, my god. - Robert...
妈的，妈的，妈的，妈的，妈的。
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
-我的天啊。他妈的什么?-我该怎么办?我该怎么办?
- Oh, my god. What the fuck? - What do I do? What do I do?
只是不动。
Just don't move.
耶稣!
Jesus!
-我的天啊!——基督!
- Oh, my god! - Christ!
-它咬你了吗?-不，我不这么认为。
- Did it bite you? - No, I don't think so.
好吧。
Okay.
爸爸小心些而已。
Dad be careful.
哦,狗屎。罗伯特，你还好吗?
Oh, shit. Robert, are you okay?
梅尔，把活塞扔给我。
Mel, throw me that plunger.
梅尔,小心。
Mel, careful.
妈的,我很抱歉。他妈的。
Shit, I'm sorry. Fuck.
——耶稣,耶稣。-该死，该死，该死。
- Jesus, Jesus. - Shit, shit, shit.
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
它会咬你的!
It's gonna bite you!
-爸爸，它会咬你的。-你在干什么?
- Dad, it's gonna bite you. - What are you doing?
-我的天啊!-我的天啊!哦,我的上帝!
- Oh, my god! - Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
小心些而已。别这样，会加重病情的。
Be careful. Stop, it's gonna aggravate it.
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my god!
——罗伯特!——爸爸,停!
- Robert! - Dad, stop!
——走开!——罗伯特!
- Go away! - Robert!
他妈的……
Fuck...
去你妈的,蛇!
Fuck you, snake!
-不见了吗?-我他妈要把你全家都吃了。
- Is it gone? - I'll fucking eat your whole fucking family.
是啊!
Yeah!
等一下…
Wait a minute...
我们应该吃掉它吗?
Should we have eaten it?
——恶心。不。-蛇加奶酪!奶酪加额外的蛇!
- Gross. No. - Snakes with extra cheese! Cheese with extra snakes!
我不知道怎么吃蛇，你呢?
I don't know how to eat a snake, do you?
是的，你只要把它捡起来
Yeah, you just pick it up
然后把脑袋咬下来，像奥兹一样。
and bite the head off, like ozzy.
那不是一只蝙蝠吗?
Wasn't that a bat?
蛇就是不会飞的蝙蝠。
Snakes are just bats that can't fly.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
再告诉我。
Tell me again.
告诉你吧，宝贝?
Tell you what, baby?
你知道。好吗?
You know what. Please?
好吧。你想让我从哪里开始?
Okay. Where do you want me to start?
告诉我你有多胖，妈妈。
Tell me about how big and fat you were, mom.
嘿。
Hey.
我看起来像是在走私
It looked like I was smuggling
我的衬衫下面有一个巨大的西瓜，
a big, gigantic watermelon underneath my shirt,
但那下面只有你。
but all that was under there was you.
我说"耐心点，宝贝。我需要你有耐心。”
I was saying, "Patience, baby. I need you to have Patience."
因为你当时还没去医院。
Because you weren't at the hospital yet.
你在沃尔玛。
You were at a Walmart.
这是正确的。
That's right.
你和娘娘腔。但是娘娘腔是我的年龄。
You and sissy. But sissy was my age.
不，娘娘腔更年轻一点，但没错，
No, sissy was a little bit younger, but yes,
娘娘腔是……和我们在一起。
sissy was... was there with us.
你在买什么?
What were you buying?
一个披萨,因为?
A pizza, because?
你厌倦了一直做饭。
You were tired of cooking all the time.
哦。是的,这是正确的。
Oh. Yes, that's right.
我怀孕九个月了，非常疲惫。
I was nine months pregnant, and I was exhausted.
爸爸在哪里呢?
Where was dad?
我不记得了。
I don't remember.
爸爸，我出生的时候你在哪里?
Dad, where were you when I was born?
他在保龄球馆喝醉了。
He was drunk at a bowling alley.
不,不喜欢。
No, don't.
妈妈,我累了。
Mommy, I'm tired.
只要闭上你的眼睛，宝贝。
Just close your eyes baby.
我累了，妈妈，我累了。
I'm tired, mommy, I'm tired.
是的…我也累了。
Yeah... I'm tired too.
-什么事?-嘘…
- What is it? - Shh...
-我想是只狗。——一只狗?
- I think it's a dog. - A dog?
——等待。-我的天啊。
- Wait. - Oh, my god.
——鲍比!——鲍比!该死的!
- Bobby! - Bobby! God damn it!
不,不!
No, don't!
他在舔我的手，伙计们。
He's licking my hand, you guys.
谁是好孩子?谁是好孩子?
Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy?
你是，你是。
You are, you are.
等等，那真的是狗吗?
Wait, is that actually a dog?
是的,检查。
Yeah, check.
哦,我的上帝。这是……它实际上是一只狗。
Oh, my god. It's... it's actually a dog.
——是吗?-好吧，小心点
- Is it? - All right, well, be careful.
你不知道那东西有多烂。
You don't know what kind of shit that thing has.
你认为是斑点吗?我想是斑点。
Do you think it's spot? I think it's spot.
小不点，是你吗?是的，不是吗?
Spot, is that you boy? It is, isn't it?
大家都说你被埋在后院了。但事实并非如此，对吧?
Everybody said you're buried in the backyard. But that isn't true, right?
你刚跑掉，现在又来救我们。
You just ran away and now you've come to save us.
谁是好孩子?谁是好孩子?
Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy?
我是个好孩子!
I'm a good boy!
哦,我的上帝!的帮助!的帮助!
Oh, my god! Help! Help!
哦,我的上帝!的帮助!哦,我的上帝!的帮助!
Oh, my god! Help! Oh, my god! Help!
的帮助!哦,我的上帝!
Help! Oh, my god!
它为什么会说话?它为什么会说话?
Why did it talk? Why did it talk?
放了我女儿，我他妈的杀了你!
Let my daughter go, I'll fucking kill you!
天啊，救救我!
Oh, my god, help me!
我要杀了你!
I'll kill you!
梅尔!
Mel!
我很抱歉，我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
天呐
Holy shit.
他要是回来，我就打烂他的脑袋。
He comes back, I'll break his goddamn skull.
大多数东西不是舌头被扯掉就死了吗?
Don't most things die with their tongues ripped out?
我看起来像什么?什么他妈的医生?
What do I look like? Some kind of fucking doctor?
我们至少得试一试，对吧?
Well, we at least need to try, right?
试着什么?
Try what?
我们还没有吃。
We haven't eaten.
梅尔，你真是个变态。
Mel, you're one sick fuck.
在这里。
Here.
妈妈，我也要吃舌头吗?
Mom, do I have to eat the tongue, too?
是的,宝贝。
Yes, baby.
好吧，我们得一小口一小口地吃
Okay, we have to eat this in tiny bites
因为它很难咀嚼，但很容易窒息，
because it'll be tough to chew but easy to choke on,
所以我们必须小心。
so we have to be careful.
再在这里待一天，我可能会被咬一口
One more day in here I'd probably take a chomp
从那个变态的老二里。
out of that creep's dick.
这是恶心。
That's disgusting.
是啊，鸡巴是用来尿尿的，不是用来吃东西的，爸爸。
Yeah, dicks are for peeing, not eating, dad.
好吧，我先试试。
Well, I'll try it first.
是我发现的，对吧?
I'm the one who caught it, right?
啊!
Ah!
你还好吗?
Oh, are you okay?
-再给我一杯。-你确定?
- Give me another. - You sure?
是的，你们所有人。我们需要吃东西。
Yeah, all of you. We need to eat.
怎么一切都搞砸了?
How did everything get so fucked up?
你知道发生了什么。
You know what happened.
你很清楚发生了什么。
You know exactly what happened.
真实的。
True.
乔。
Joe.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我的天，给我滚出去!
My god, get the fuck out of here!
滚，你这个变态。
Go, you fucking creep.
-我很抱歉——这很好。
- I'm so sorry. - It's fine.
我到哪儿他就跟到哪儿。
He follows me everywhere.
是啊，真是个蠢蛋。
Yeah, what a fucking dunce.
他为什么就不能接受暗示呢?
Why couldn't he just take a fucking hint?
回想起来，我们不应该对他的所作所为感到惊讶。
In retrospect, we shouldn't be surprised at what he did.
不。
No.
你什么都不用说。
You don't have to say anything.
你怎么想，我就怎么想。
Anything you think, I think.
如何?
How?
我不明白发生了什么事。
I don't understand what's happening.
没人要你这么做。
No one's asking you to.
我们得做点什么，别再胡说八道了，对吧?
We had to do something to stop from talking shit, right?
我们不得不。
We had to.
帮我个忙?
Give me a hand?
对不起,现货。
Sorry, spot.
啊。
Ugh.
这个咒语应该很简单。
The spell should be pretty simple.
黑帮总是这么做。
The mob does it all the time.
暴徒吗?
The mob?
它能让人们不再说你的坏话。
It convinces people to stop talking shit about you.
给他们一个严厉的警告，告诉他们你不是什么大人物
Gives them a stern warning that you aren't someone
被人玩弄。
to be fucked with.
所以，给这混蛋一个警告，好吗?
So, let's give this motherfucker a warning, shall we?
马上就到。
Back to you in a second.
我想他的全名是约瑟夫。
I think his full name is Joseph.
我不确定这有多重要。
I'm not sure it matters that much.
抱歉，是我妈。
Sorry, it's just my mom.
这样的话，他说的任何关于我的话都会变成针对他的。
This way, anything he tries to say about me will be turned against him.
-我爱你…——嘘。
- I love you... - Shh.
我也爱你。
I love you too.
这就是我们让他受苦的方式。
This is how we really make him suffer.
起床了。
Get up.
什么?爸爸?
What? Dad?
——起床。——为什么?
- Get up. - Why?
——爸爸,为什么?-当我让你做什么事的时候
- Dad, why? - When I tell you to do something,
你是你做了还是质疑我?
do you you do it or you question me?
我做这件事。
I do it.
然后去做。
Then do it.
你盯着她看什么?是我在跟你说话。
What are you looking at her for? I'm the one talking to you.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
鲍比和我要试试。
Bobby and I are gonna try something.
试着什么?
Try what?
-看到了吗?——看看?
- You see that? - See what?
该死的开放。你看到了吗?
The goddamn opening. Do you see it?
是的。
Yes.
好。我需要你把它过一遍。
Good. I need you to go through it.
什么?
What?
我,我不能。
I, I can't.
你都不试一试?
You're not even gonna try?
你甚至都没试过。
You didn't even try.
你试一试又有什么坏处?
What is it gonna hurt if you just try?
你为什么一直看着她?
Why do you keep looking at her?
我不知道!
I don't know!
我是你爸爸，对吧?
I'm your daddy, right?
是的。
Yes.
你想让你爸爸妈妈开心，对吧?
And you want to make your mommy and daddy happy, right?
是的。
Yes.
那你得帮我们离开这里。
Then you need to help us get out of here.
你得从那里爬过去，挤过去。
You need to climb through there, squeeze through, please.
-不要做…- - - - - -闭嘴!
- Do not do... - Shut up!
来吧,鲍比。你能做到的。我相信你。这样做。
Come on, Bobby. You can do it. I believe in you. Do it.
你甚至都没努力!
You're not even trying!
,但是……-来吧，你他妈能行的。
- But... - Come on, you can fucking do it.
别他妈孩子气了，
Stop being a fucking baby about it,
从那里挤过去。
just squeeze through there.
来吧，该死的。挤压!
Come on, god damn it. Squeeze!
来吧。
Come on.
-该死。——爸爸!
- God damn it. - Dad!
你差不多了。想做就做。
You're almost there. Just do it.
通过。
Go through.
该死，挤过去!
God damn it, squeeze through there!
——爸爸!停!-该死!
- Dad! Stop! - God damn it!
他妈的什么?他进不去!
What the fuck? He's not gonna fit!
挤过!
Squeeze through!
放开他!你是谁? !
Get the fuck off of him! Who are you?!
-你他妈在干什么?-你他妈在干什么?
- What the fuck are you doing? - What the fuck are you doing?
-那是我们的儿子。-我有个计划我是想让大家离开这里!
- That's our son. - I have a plan. I'm trying to get us out of here!
-你要把我们的儿子…-我们会死在这里吗!
- You're putting our son in the... - What are we gonna die out here!
现在他倒在地上了。过来这里!
Now he's on the fucking ground. Come over here!
鲍比?哦,我的上帝。
Bobby? Oh, my god.
鲍比?鲍比!鲍比,没关系!
Bobby? Bobby! Bobby, it's okay!
加油！加油我们到浴缸里去。
Come on, come on. Let's get in the tub.
我们到浴缸里去。没关系。
Let's get in the tub. It's okay.
没事的，来吧。我们到浴缸里去。伙计们!伙计们!
It's okay, come on. Let's get in the tub. Guys! Guys!
在浴缸里，在浴缸里!到浴缸里去。
In the tub, in the tub! Get in the tub.
——人!他妈的!-什么也没做!
- Guys! Fuck! - Ain't doing nothing!
伙计们，你们能不能停下来?鲍比出事了。
Guys, will you fucking stop? Something happened to Bobby.
我认为……天啊，我觉得是蛇。
I think... oh, my god, I think it was the snake.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
-去拿马桶盖。——什么?
- Get the toilet lid. - What?
他妈的马桶顶，抓住它!
The top of the fucking toilet, get it!
好的,准备好了吗?
Okay, ready?
哦，天哪，它打中你了吗?
Oh, god, did it get you?
——嗯。-我的天啊。
- Uh-huh. - Oh, my gosh.
-来，让我看看。鲍比。-让我看看。
- Here, let me see. Bobby. - Let me see.
阻止它。哦,天哪。
Stop it. Oh, gosh.
——好的。你能把领带给我吗?什么,为什么?
- Okay. Can you get me your tie? - What, why?
-止血带。-不，我们得吸出他的毒液。
- For a tourniquet. - No, we need to suck the venom out of him.
不，我觉得我们得确保毒液不会进入他的心脏。
No, I think we need to make sure the venom doesn't go to his heart.
把你的领带给我。
Give me your goddamn tie.
好的，好的，等一下，等一下。
Okay, okay, one second, one second.
好吧。等待。
Okay. Wait.
——没有。不。——鲍比!
- No. No. - Bobby!
哦,我的天啊。你能抱抱他吗?
Oh, my gosh. Can you hold him?
我做不到。
I can't do this.
好吧。
All right.
你拿到了吗?
Did you get it?
你拿到了吗?你拿到了吗?
Did you get it? Did you get it?
你拿到了吗?
Did you get it?
我…我不知道，也许吧。
I... I don't know, maybe.
你在这里很安全。宝贝?宝贝，听我说。
You're safe in here. Baby? Baby, listen to me.
-我们需要水。-好的，我马上给你拿水。只是坚持。
- We need water. - Okay, I'll get you water in a minute. Just hold on.
草泥马。
Motherfucker.
-我知道，放松，试着放松。——草泥马。
- I know, just relax, try to relax. - Motherfucker.
草泥马。傻瓜。草泥马。
Motherfucker. Fucker. Motherfucker.
你他妈的混蛋。
You fucking motherfucker.
鲍比会没事吧?妈妈，鲍比没事吧?
Is Bobby gonna be okay? Mom, is Bobby gonna be okay?
是的，他会没事的!鲍比?
Yes, he's gonna be fine! Right, Bobby?
-会没事的。——草泥马。你他妈的混蛋!
- Gonna be fine. - Motherfucker. You fucking motherfucker!
你混蛋。你不要脸的混蛋!
You motherfucker. You motherfucking motherfucker!
你笨蛋!你不要脸的混蛋!
You fucker! You motherfucking motherfucker!
你,笨蛋!
You fuckers!
你娘!
You motherfuckers!
你娘!放我出去!
You motherfuckers! Let me the fuck out of here!
我要杀了你!
I'll fucking kill you!
他妈的把门打开!该死的!
Open the fucking door! God damn it!
天啊，天啊!
Oh, god, oh, god!
鲍比?鲍比，我很抱歉。
Bobby? Bobby, I'm so sorry.
鲍比,我…
Bobby, I...
很抱歉，这都是我的错。
I'm so sorry, this is all my fault.
什么?你在说什么?这不是你的错。
What? What are you talking about? This is not your fault.
-都是我的错。我很抱歉。-不不不不嘘。
- This is all my fault. I'm so sorry. - No, no, no, no, no. Shh.
不会有事的。好吧?你会没事的。
It's gonna be okay. Okay? You're gonna be okay.
蜂蜜。这不是任何人的错。这不是任何人的错。
Honey. It's nobody's fault. It's nobody's fault.
好吧?
Okay?
喂?喂?
Hello? Hello?
这是怎么呢你还好吗?
What's going on? Are you okay?
嘿,谁有?
Hey, who's there?
我们在这里。
We're over here.
我们需要帮助。
We need help.
我儿子被咬了。
My son was bit.
我儿子被咬了。的帮助!
My son was bit. Help!
-你看见谁了吗?-我什么都没看到。
- Do you see someone? - I don't see shit.
喂?
Hello?
拜托，我们需要个医生。
Please, we need a fucking doctor.
好吧，跟着我的声音。
All right, follow my voice.
哦,耶稣基督。
Oh, Jesus Christ.
我们不能。
We can't.
我们被困住了。你跟着我的声音走。
We're stuck. You follow my voice.
请。我们……我儿子需要治疗
Please. We... my son needs medical attention.
好了，好了，等一下。
Okay, okay, hold on.
我想我看到你了。等一等。
I think I see you. Hold on.
等一下，我得…不…
Hold on, I have to... no...
那是什么……什么?
What's that... what?
哦,上帝…
Oh, god...
哦,上帝!不!
Oh, god! No!
你看到什么了吗?
Do you see anything?
没有，我什么也没看到。
No, I don't see anything.
但我觉得我们应该把门关上一段时间。
But I think we should keep the door closed for a little while.
但是鲍比呢?
But what about Bobby?
给我闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
-我觉得我们应该…-你们都给我闭嘴!
- I think we should ta... - Shut the fuck up, all of you!
好吧，我想我们可以再谈谈。
Okay, I think we can talk again.
但我们还是要注意量，以防万一。
But we should still watch our volumes, just in case.
万一什么?
In case of what?
你在外面看到了什么?
What did you see out there?
我不知道。
I don't know.
真的有人向他开枪了吗?
Did someone really shoot that guy?
也许他在射击什么东西。
Maybe he was shooting something.
什么东西吗?
Something?
我不知道。
I don't know.
鲍比需要帮助。
Bobby needs help.
我们都需要帮助。
We all need help.
他需要医生，罗伯特。
He needs a doctor, Robert.
你以为我不知道吗?
You think I don't know that?
咬一口会杀了他吗?
Can that bite kill him?
我想我把所有东西都吸出来了。我不…我不知道。
I think I sucked everything out. I don't... I don't know.
天啊，到底发生了什么?
Jesus Christ, what the fuck happened?
我很害怕。
I'm scared.
我也是,亲爱的。
Me too, sweetheart.
我们该怎么办?
What should we do?
伙计们，我们该怎么办?
Guys, what should we do?
梅尔，你他妈为什么一直问我们该怎么办!
Mel, why the fuck do you keep asking us what should we do?!
你知道的我们都知道。
We know exactly what you know.
这他妈没什么，好吗?好吧?
Which is fucking nothing, okay? Okay?
是的。
Yeah.
好吧,我很抱歉。
Okay, I'm sorry.
我不知道我们该怎么办。
I don't know what we're gonna do.
我不知道外面发生了什么。
I don't know what happened out there.
我不知道谁杀了谁。我不知道他们为什么要杀他。
I don't know who shot who. I don't know why they shot him.
我不知道我们还能不能走出这间浴室去寻找答案。
I don't know if we're ever gonna get out of this bathroom to find out.
我都不知道我想不想知道。
I don't even know if I wanna find out.
我不知道鲍比会不会没事。
I don't know if Bobby's gonna be okay.
我现在什么都不知道。
I don't know goddamn much about anything right now.
我们杀了他。
We killed him.
我知道。我们混乱的。
I know. We fucked up.
我们吗?
We?
我们是一条船上的，不是吗?
We're in this together, aren't we?
是的，我们是一条船上的。
Yeah, we're in this together.
谢谢你没有抛弃我。
Thank you for not abandoning me.
我不会的，好吗?
Hey, I would never, okay?
这是一个巫术咒语。
It was a necromancy spell.
-我们用在乔身上的那个?-不，梅勒妮，不是乔。我，我把它用在了自己身上。
- That we used on Joe? - No, melly, not Joe. Me, I used it on myself.
我告诉过你我死了，至少我以为我死了。
I told you I was dead, or at least I thought I was dead.
如何?
How?
这很复杂，现在开始讲细节，
It's complicated, and getting into the details now,
那并不重要。对吧?
it's not important. Right?
重点是，这种特殊的咒语
The point is this, that specific kind of spell
是用来让人起死回生的。
is supposed to bring back people from the dead.
我的内心已经死了。
And something inside of me was dead.
所以它只在理论上有意义
So it only makes sense theoretically
它可以…是可行的。
that it could... would work.
干的?
Did it?
我，我以为我好多了，我痊愈了。
I, I thought I was better, that I was healed.
好吧,你呢?
Well, are you?
我这几天一直觉得不舒服。
I haven't felt right in the past couple of days.
我还以为是乔给我的那些假情色的屁话。
And I thought maybe it was all the deepfake porno bullshit Joe pulled on me.
但现在我怀疑是别的原因。
But now I suspect it's something else.
一些更邪恶的东西。
Something a little more evil.
艾米，你说什么都没用。
Amy, you're not making any sense.
如果一直以来死去的不是我呢?
What if it wasn't me who was dead all this time?
如果我体内有什么东西死了呢?
What if something was inside me and that's what was dead?
我施了咒语，它就醒了吗?
And when I performed the spell, it woke up?
——艾米,我…-一直在等一个完美的时刻
- Amy, I... - It's just been waiting for the perfect moment
来宣布它的到来。
to announce its arrival.
-我不认为…-这就是为什么舌头拼错的原因。
- I don't think... - It has to be why the tongue spell went so wrong.
我是说，我知道我们把牛的舌头换成了狗的舌头，
I mean, I know we substituted a dog's tongue for a cow's,
但我的意思是，天哪，发生的事本不该发生。
but still, I mean, holy shit, what happened shouldn't have happened.
除非主持仪式的人心里藏着什么东西。
Unless the person who conducted the ritual had something hiding inside of them.
超出人类的东西。某物
Something beyond human. Something...
一些什么?
Something what?
恶魔的东西。
Something diabolical.
他怎么还没去看你?
Why hasn't he checked on you yet?
-为什么没有…——迪。不玩聋。
- Why hasn't who... - Dee. Don't play deaf.
我知道你听到了。你不觉得他担心吗?
I know you hear me. Don't you think he's worried?
我觉得现在谈这个不太合适。
I really don't think now is the best time to talk about this.
我不是想当混蛋，该死的。
I'm not trying to be an asshole, god damn it.
我只是想说我们得离开这里
I'm just saying we need to get out of here
或者我们受骗的。
or we're fucked.
特别是现在。
Especially now.
你们在说谁?
Who are you guys talking about?
没关系,宝贝。没关系。我知道。
It's okay, baby. It's okay. I know.
好吗?
Well?
我跟他说如果他不…
I told him if he didn't...
他半夜还没收到我的消息，
He didn't hear from me by midnight,
那么可能发生了什么事。
then something might have happened.
像什么?
Something like what?
我们真的不应该谈这个。
We really shouldn't get into this.
不好意思，来的不是时候吗?
Oh, I'm sorry, is this a bad time?
我不知道你会有什么反应。我很害怕。
I didn't know how you'd react. I was scared.
害怕什么?
Scared of what?
的你。
Of you.
你以为我会怎么做?伤害你吗?
What'd you think I'd do? Hurt you?
——也许。-我的天啊我伤害过你吗?
- Maybe. - Oh, Jesus fucking Christ. Have I ever hurt you?
不要忽略我。
Stop ignoring me.
你们他妈的在说什么?
What the fuck are you guys talking about?
我给过你很多机会。
I gave you chances, plenty of chances.
我给了你很多年的机会。
I gave you years and years of chances.
年?你想谈谈岁月吗?
Years? You wanna talk about years?
我会跟你说他妈的几年。
I'll talk to you about fucking years.
你他妈整天都在说几年的事。
Talk about years all fucking day long.
你觉得你能离开这里吗?
You think you're ever getting out of here?
你觉得我们能走路吗
You think any of us is ever gonna walk
-又从这扇门出去?——这就够了!
- out of this door again? - That's enough!
你最…!
You're the most...!
你是我这辈子见过的最痴心妄想的贱人!
You're the most delusional bitch I've ever met in my entire life!
-妈妈…-别吵了。请停止战斗。
- Mom... - Please stop fighting. Please stop fighting.
你又吓到孩子了，亲爱的。
You're scaring the kids again, dear.
妈妈。
Mommy.
很疼，全身都在燃烧。
It hurts, everything burns.
所有的烧伤。
Everything burns.
他的心跳……
His heartbeat...
鲍比，你他妈的冷静点。
Bobby, you gotta calm the fuck down.
你他妈给我冷静下来。
You gotta calm the fuck down right now.
-好吧，那没用-你他妈的想让我做什么?
- Okay, that isn't helping. - What the fuck do you want me to do?
我不知道。不是。
I don't know. Just not that.
好吧,宝贝。好了，宝贝，没事了。
Okay, baby. Okay, baby, it's okay.
我要你好好深呼吸，好吗?
I want you to take nice, deep breaths, okay?
好吧，和我一起做。
Okay, do it with me.
深呼吸。
Deep breath.
很容易。很容易。
Nice and easy. Nice and easy.
这很好。这很好。
That's good. That's good.
妈妈，再告诉我一次。
Mom, tell me again.
告诉你吧，宝贝?
Tell you what, baby?
你知道的,请。
You know, please.
我们想买个冷冻披萨，
We were trying to buy a frozen pizza,
你觉得你在我肚子里待得够久了。
and you decided you had been in my belly long enough.
你又大又胖的肚子。
Your big, fat belly.
像一个西瓜。
Like a watermelon.
和我…
And I...
我走不动了，我只是…
I couldn't walk anymore and I was just...
很疼，而且你踢我很用力。
It hurt so badly and you were kicking me so hard.
他们叫救护车了吗?
Did they call an ambulance?
他们确定了。
They sure did.
在我们等救护车的时候，
And while we were waiting for the ambulance,
茜茜坐在我旁边，握着我的手。
sissy sat down next to me and held my hand.
她看着我说，
And she looked at me and she said,
“一切都会好起来的。”
"everything's gonna be okay."
你只需要勇敢一点，再多等一会儿。
You just have to be brave and wait little bit longer.
“不会有什么坏事发生的。一切都会解决的。”
"Nothing bad is gonna happen. And everything will work out."
你知道吗，宝贝?她是对的。
And you know what, baby? She was right.
她帮助我变得勇敢和坚强。
She helped me be brave and strong.
我们等着救护车来。
And we waited for the ambulance to come.
当他们来的时候，他们把你从我身上拖了出来。
And when they came, they pulled you out of me.
就在那里，冷冻食品区那层。
Right there, on the frozen food section floor.
所以我知道你会没事的。
And that's why I know you're gonna be okay.
娘娘腔也会没事的。
And sissy's gonna be okay.
一切都会好起来的，会有人来的。
And everything's gonna be okay and someone's gonna come.
有人会来把那棵树移开，然后打开那扇门。
Someone's gonna come and move that tree and open that door.
所有人都会在外面等着。
And everyone will be waiting outside.
这样生活就会更好。
And life will be better.
一切都会好起来的。
And everything will be okay.
你只要再坚持一会儿，好吗，宝贝?
You just have to hold on a little bit longer, okay, baby?
只要再坚持一段时间。好吧?
Just have to hold on a little bit longer. Okay?
只是信任…
Just trust...
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
不!宝贝!
No! Baby!
我的宝贝，来吧!
My baby boy, come on!
不，我们只需要再等一会儿!请。
No, we just have to wait a little longer! Please.
你从哪儿弄来的?
Where did you get this?
有些秘密是不该被揭露的。
Some secrets aren't meant to be revealed.
现在我。
Now me.
让我流血。
Make me bleed.
你无法解决不可避免的事情。
You can't fix the inevitable.
他妈的。
Fuck.
天啊，为什么还没完?
God, why won't it stop?
等等，鲍比在哪儿?
Wait, where's, where's Bobby?
他一直在的地方，宝贝。
Where he's always been, baby.
妈妈，我胃疼。
Mom, my stomach hurts.
你为什么不接我电话?
Why weren't you answering my calls?
我…我感觉不舒服。我认为……我觉得我体内有某种东西。
I... I don't feel good. I think... I think there's something inside me.
我们都会因为你而死。
We're all gonna die because of you.
——什么?-你不知道你自己的女儿是个女巫?
- What? - You didn't know your own daughter was a witch?
你真他妈的是个好妈妈。
Some fucking mother you are.
-是真的吗，梅尔?-请帮帮我。
- Is that true, Mel? - Please, help me.
不喜欢。这是一个陷阱。
Don't. It's a trap.
她的一个女巫陷阱。
One of her witch traps.
你想帮她，她就会骂你。
You try to help her and she'll curse you.
不，有点不对劲。
No, something is wrong.
给我点时间，好吗?
Just give me a second, will you?
我在哪儿?
Where am I?
你觉得呢?
Where do you think?
哦,上帝。
Oh, god.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
妈的，我怎么了?
Fuck, what's wrong with me?
在那之后，你…你把这些都喝了。
After what happened, you... You drank this, all of it.
你都不能给我留点，对吧?
And you couldn't even leave any for me, could you?
后……之后发生了什么事?
After... after what happened?
这都是我的错。
This is all my fault.
什么?
What?
这一切都是因为我。
All of this is because of me.
-不，不是…-不，不，听着你不听。
- No, it's not... - No, no, just listen. You're not listening.
昨晚……妈的，不是昨晚。
Last night... Fuck, not last night.
这一切开始的那晚
The night all of this started,
艾米和我…
Amy and I...
我们做了坏事。
We did something bad.
我不明白你的意思。
I don't understand.
艾米病了，好吗?就像，真的，真的病了。我们……
Amy was sick, okay? Like, really, truly sick. We...
我们以为她体内有东西。
We thought that there was something inside her.
也许一些…不好的事情，比如……
Maybe something... Something bad, like a...
就像恶魔或灵魂。
Like a demon or spirit.
梅尔，你他妈在胡说些什么?
Mel, what the fuck are you babbling about?
学校的一个男孩死了。
A boy at school died.
这都是因为我们。
It was because of us.
我们施了咒语，
We did a spell,
让他停止散播谣言，
something to just make him stop spreading rumors,
编造谎言。
making up lies.
他本不该死的。
He was never supposed to die.
但是出了问题。
But something went wrong.
那天晚上，他睡觉时舌头哽住了。
That night, he choked on his tongue while he was sleeping.
被自己的舌头噎死是不可能的。
It's impossible to choke on your own tongue.
嗯,它的发生而笑。
Well, it happened.
谁知道接下来会发生什么
And who knows what would have kept happening
如果我们不阻止的话。
if we hadn't put a stop to it.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
-结束…-对艾米的迷恋结束了。
- Put an end to... - An end to the thing possessing Amy.
一个恶魔?
A demon?
我们，我们不知道那是什么。
Well, we, we didn't know what it was.
只说这很糟糕。
Just that it was bad.
-你做了什么?-我们想杀了它。
- What did you do? - We tried to kill it.
我们施了个咒语，是在网上找到的。
We did a spell, something we found online.
在线吗?
Online?
我认为……
I think...
我觉得发生的一切
I think that everything that's been happening
是因为我们施了咒语。
is because of a spell we did.
我觉得我们搞砸了。
I think we messed up really bad.
如果你说的是真的，
If that's true, what you just said,
你之前怎么什么都没说?
why didn't you say anything before?
-我很害怕。-啊，勇敢到足以毁灭世界
- I was afraid. - Ah, brave enough to destroy the world
但不敢承认，是吗?
but too chicken shit to own up to it, is that it?
什么?
What?
我要你看看那个浴缸。
I want you to look in that tub.
我要你看看你死去的弟弟。
I want you to look at your dead brother.
你闻到了吗?
Do you smell that?
这是他的尸体。
That's his corpse.
分解、腐烂。
Decomposing, rotting.
都是因为你和你的巫毒女友!
And all because of you and your voodoo bitch girlfriend!
我希望你在网上玩的时间值得你杀了你的家人。
I hope your fun little time on the Internet was worth murdering your family.
对不起，对不起，对不起。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
你再这么跟我女儿说话我就割了你的喉咙。
Speak that way to my daughter again and I'll slit your fucking throat.
我期待着这一天的到来。
I look forward to the day.
我很抱歉。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我们得吃掉他。
We need to eat him.
把他单独留下。
Leave him alone.
这是我们唯一的选择。
It's our only choice.
见鬼去吧。
Like hell it is.
我们必须。
We have to.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我他妈的什么也看不见!
I can't fucking see anything!
我想我是瞎了。耶稣基督。
I think I'm blind. Jesus Christ.
你一直在不停地吸酒精湿巾。
You have been sucking alcohol wipes non-stop.
-难怪你他妈的瞎了。-我们得找个东西割肉。
- No wonder you're fucking blind. - We need to find something to cut the flesh.
你他妈的别碰他!
Don't you fucking touch him!
停止代理歇斯底里!
Stop acting hysterical!
你们这些该死的巫师最好别再阻止我了。
Now none of you fucking witches better try and stop me.
我们要吃的。
We gotta eat.
天啊，那是什么鬼东西!
Jesus Christ, what the fuck is that?!
那是什么?那是什么鬼东西?
What is that? What in the hell is that?
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
我想我明白了。
I think I got it.
是吗?
Yes?
当然可以。
Of course.
是的。
Yes.
不。
No.
我明白了。
I understand.
是的。
Yes.
你他妈在干什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
搞什么，罗伯特?
What the fuck, Robert?
这很有道理，不是吗?
It makes sense, doesn't it?
是她先开始的。
She's the one who started it.
所以只有她能结束这一切。
So she's the only one who can end it.
什么?这是艾米吗?
What? Was that Amy?
结束这场噩梦，你个女巫。
End this nightmare, you witch.
女巫!
Witch!
女巫,女巫!
Witch, witch!
杀了女巫，杀了女巫!
Kill the witch, kill the witch!
杀死女巫!
Kill the witch!
离开!别管她!
Get away! Leave her alone!
杀死女巫。杀死女巫!
Kill the witch. Kill the witch!
-杀了女巫!-离她远点!别管她!
- Kill the witch! - Leave her alone! Leave her alone!
杀死女巫!
Kill the witch!
我们一直都在这里吗?
Have we always been here?
什么?
What?
门外什么都没有。
There's nothing outside the door.
没有什么……
There's nothing...
什么都没有。
Nothing.
好吧……
Okay...
好吧,好吧…
Okay, okay...
我要出去看看，我要…
I'm gonna go out and see, I'm just gonna...
我只是想看看。我马上就回来。
I'm just gonna see. I'll be back.
妈妈?
Mom?
艾米!
Amy!
我曾经割伤过自己。
I used to cut myself.
——梅丽莎!——妈妈?
- Melissa! - Mom?
妈妈……我看到艾米。
Mom... I saw Amy.
——我知道。我知道。-我看到艾米了
- I know. I know. - I saw Amy.
我知道。我知道。
I know. I know.
我知道。
I know.
妈妈,外面是什么?
Mom, what's outside?
不会有事的。不会有事的。
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
不会有事的。
It's gonna be okay.
不会有事的。不会有事的。
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
不会有事的。一切都会没事的。
It's gonna be okay. Everything's gonna be okay.
一切都会没事的。一切都会没事的。
Everything's gonna be okay. Everything's gonna be okay.